[{"answer": "God damnit!  my friend, my friend wants to know why you break up", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "'K.  She says she's been wantin' to break up for a while, and it's nothing against you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "'K.  She says she's been wantin' to break up for a while, and it's nothing against you", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No dude, I'm out. Go talk to her yourself. Be poetic", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "As soon as possible", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oooh, you are such a sweetie. Come here, youuu", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend, you need to go talk to my friend for me right now!  All this time I've been trying to have my friends do all the talking for me! Now I realize I need her friends to do it! Tell her I love her", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Okay, so what's the most romantic thing I can think of", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It's a little stuffed bear dressed as a rabbit", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well yeah, but, but, hey,  hey Lexus? Well I was thinking, well, I was thinking that we shoul", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Go away Mom! Leave me alone", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You'd like to wait till I was dead, wouldn't you? You'd like to see maggots eat my face", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh well, uh I kinda don't have any money left. Unh, I spent it all on Raisins the last six times", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, I really wanna see you too, baby. Eh don't, don't worry. I'll get more mone", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Dude, you haven't drank your coffee", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You can't be a no", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend, this is it. Time to stop feeling sorry for yourself and come home! Everyone cares about you and everyone wants you back", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yeah. She is", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hi guys. Can I take your order", "docId": "South-Park-Raisins.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I shouldn't? Where I supposed to be working", "qsentId": 20}]